In the previous version, if you want to share fabric or fabric documents to Closet, you need to save them to the computer and then upload them through the browser.
Starting from the 2026.0 version, you can complete the upload of the fabric and the fabric and simplify the entire process.
First, let's try to upload the fabric applied on the clothing to the object window.
In the fabric options card, select the fabric you want to upload.
After selecting, see the property editor at the bottom.
At the top right of the property editor, you will find the newly uploaded Closet icon.
Clicking on the icon will display two options, new content and new version.
If this is your first time uploading assets to Closet, please select new content.
If you want to upload the modified version of the existing file to Closet, please select the new version.
For example, if you want to upload a new asset, select new content.
Set the preview image in the saved fabric window.
After clicking the confirm button, immediately jump to the upload page of the Closet account related to it.
Complete the quick and simple upload.
In addition to the fabric,
You can also upload the photo, button, buttonhole, eye, name line, seamstress spell,
attached and zipper directly to Closet.
But please note that for the seamstress spell,
Currently only support new content options.
It is currently not possible to update it as a new version.
Through the upload file function,
You can manage and share fabric and fabric resources more efficiently.
Enjoy the infinite cooperation experience.
In order to continuously optimize the Closet user experience,
We have updated the content page and workspace interface of Closet.
When the 3D file is uploaded to Closet,
Users will first see the cover part.
You can fill in the main information through the lower paragraph.
For example, classification.
You can also add a label.
By clicking the settings button in the upper right corner,
You can define the content displayed in the first page.
You can drag and drop or delete the displayed content.
You can also check other detailed information in the label page above.
For example, details, versions, link content, etc.
The next part is the viewfinder.
We have made some changes to the 3D viewfinder.
Click on the label in the upper right corner.
You can see the logo and color of the file.
Click on the upper left column.
You can manage the version.
The next part is the material list.
It will display the material information according to the Closet settings.
Click on each part of the table in the material list.
You can edit the data of each material.
You can also click on the add empty line.
Here is the newly created material in Closet.
The material list is next to the measurement line POM.
It will display the measurement point data according to the Closet settings.
You can see the measurement line in the 3D viewfinder window on the right.
You can see the measurement point data in the 3D viewfinder window on the right.
You can upload other relevant articles in the attached page.
Your student will be able to edit other relevant articles.
Thank you.
Finally, you can see theị文件创建周期.
Click on the share icon in the upper right column.
You can share you website.
You can post comments.
You can click on the user's avatar to switch to the dark mode.
Go back to the Workroom page, click on the information button at the bottom, you can see the relevant information of the file.
Through the above updates, users can design and develop more smoothly.